José Sebastián Cardona Q

Backend developer

Medellín, Colombia (+57) 3186889155 Se.bass0688@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sebastian-cardona-q

I am a software developer with almost 10 years of experience. The programming language that I have used for the last five years for most is Java, being this for me, the stronger programming language.

I have worked on different projects in both the public and private spheres always adding value. I like to take on challenges of developing new features as well as correcting and detecting bugs always trying to deliver my obligations on time. I have the best attitude and I am interested in a good work environment. I am an also enthusiastic learner of VueJs and AWS products.

EXPERIENCE

Implemental Systems, Development Analyst — Apr. 2012 - Dec. 2016

- Development and creation of information migration processes into Smallword Core database as well as important personalizations to client provisioning services.
- On-site support for clients locally and internationally helping to the clients with work on in Smallworld platform and fixing development bugs and operational errors.
- Customer training on Smallworld Core and its modules.

Tech Stack: Smallworld Core, Magik

Tecnofactor, Development Analyst — Dec, 2016 - Sep, 2018

- Personalizations for VyP optimizing the cutting of raw materials.
- Development of new functionalities for proprietary software of the company RaaS.
- Outsourcing for Quipux SAS with good performance.

Tech Stack: Java, Maven

Quipux, Development Analyst — Sep. 2018 - Jun. 2019

 Improvement of vehicle tax platform of Antioquia, thereby facilitating the digitalization of the process and improving the tax collection

Tech Stack: Java, Spring Boot, Microservices

Sempli, Software Development Engineer — Jun, 2019 – Nov 2022

- Automate tasks making the credit study process faster.
- Make integrations with other usable platforms in credit study process (Zapier, Metatask, Pipedrive).
- Integrations with communication platforms like Twilio or Infobip. This got better communications with clients, offering a better service and generating new leads

Tech Stack: Java, Maven, Microservices, Spring Boot

PROJECTS

Gestión metrológica - https://www.gestionmetrologica.com/ - 2021 - 2022

 Facilitate the metrological assurance plan for labs. This platform uses some AWS products (S3, Cognito, Amplify, EC2, Postgres) Java and VueJs

SKILLS

Programming Languages: <u>Advanced:</u> Java; <u>Basic:</u> JavaScript, Python. **Frameworks and Tools:** <u>Intermediate:</u> Spring Boot, JPA; <u>Basic:</u> Node.

Data Base: Basic: Postgres, Oracle, MySQL.

Languages: Basic Professional: English; Native: Spanish.

EDUCATION

National University - Medellín, Colombia. Control Engineering, Apr 2011

CERTIFICATIONS

Oracle Certified Associate - Java SE 7 Programmer - Oracle. 2015.

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner - Amazon, 2022.